socinator.com 2019-09-13

# Terms and Privacy Policy - SociNator

We acknowledge your visit to our website. Protection of your personal and private data is the significant matter for us. By accessing our site, you need to accept the terms listed on the website and agree to our privacy policy. You should agree with the condition that, we may change any terms and conditions in future and this will be updated on the site for your preference.  
**What personal data do we gather from the visitors who visit our website, blog or app?**  
While registering or purchasing within our website, you may be asked to provide us personal or organizational information that may involve your name, email address, phone number or other details to support you with your knowledge.  
**When do we gather information from you?**  
We gather information from you when you visit, place an order, request a trial, access information on our site or give information to our customer support desk.  
**How do we use your information?**  
There are different ways we utilize your information that we gather from you when you register, sign up for our newsletter, make a purchase, browse the website, reply to a survey or marketing interaction, or some other site attributes in the following ways:

  * To update our website in order to properly serve you.
  * To offer a contest, survey, promotion or other site characteristics.
  * To immediately process your transactions.
  * To market our ads, service, and periodic email
  * To give support or other services

**How do we secure visitor information?**  
All you personal information received behind protected networks and is particularly accessible by a less number of people who have appropriate access rights on such systems and are needed to have the information confidential. With this, all sensitive credit data you supply is encrypted through Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology. When users place a purchase in order to keep the protection of their personal information we make a variety of safety measures.  
Any transactions made by the user are not processed or stored on our servers but processed by a gateway provider (Paypal).

### **Rights to Your Information According to GDPR**

GDPR stands for the General Data Protection Regulation (EU) 2016/679, which is a European Union law governing privacy and data protection for all residents of the EU. The provisions of GDPR can be also applied to how data is processed and verified (more on that later) outside the European Union.

Generally speaking, the GDPR represents a new set of rules intended to empower the citizens of the European Union to control their personal information. In accordance with the applicable laws, users are authorized to access and modify their own data held by the companies, which includes data collection, ad tracking, surveys, cookies, location data, and every other bit of a user’s “digital footprint”. Users are also entitled to transmit their personal details to other organizations. The GDPR also enforces companies to determine their in-house data security policies.

At any time through the web interface provided as part of the Services or via [contact us](https://www.adsbridge.com/contact-us) page you have the right:

  * to access your personal information that we hold;
  * to request the rectification of your personal information that we hold;
  * to request the erasure of your personal information that we hold;
  * to request to restrict processing of your personal information;
  * to object to processing of your personal information by us;
  * to request to transfer your personal information that we hold (e.g. data portability);
  * to file a complaint to a supervisory authority in your jurisdiction; and
  * to withdraw any consent related to your personal information given by you.

We will process your requests to us within 30 days. We will also notify you within and a relevant supervisory authority within 72 hours from a breach related to your personal information that we hold.

We have assigned a Data Protection Officer (DPO) who may be reached via support@socinator.com. Our DPO is tasked with ensuring that we acknowledge and abide by our data protection responsibilities.

We will not store personal information for more than 6 months from the date of your last active session on the Site or for more than 6 months from the date of termination of an agreement between Adsbridge and you (whichever is earlier).  
**Do we use ‘cookies’?**  
No, we are not using cookies to pull visitors to our site. We hold the right.  
**Is there any Third Party Disclosure?**  
We do not disclose your personal information to third parties. It does not involve website hosting partners and other parties who help us in running our website, servicing you or conducting our business, up to those parties accept to hold this information secure. We may also publish your information when we think the release is relevant to follow the law, enforce our website policies, or secure ours or others’ property, rights, or safety or for corporate action. Still, non-personally recognizable visitor information may be given to other parties for advertising, marketing, promotion or other uses.  
**Third party links:**  
Sometimes, at our choice, we may add or allow third-party products or services on our site. Separate and autonomous privacy policies are there for these third party sites. We, hence, have no obligation or responsibility for the content and actions of these linked sites.  
COPPA (Children Online Privacy Protection Act):  
If it comes to the gathering of personal information from children below age 13, the act COPPA defines Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act puts parents in charge. The COPPA rule is enforced by the Federal Trade Commission, the nation’s consumer protection agency that spells out what administrators of websites and online services need to do to protect children’s safety and privacy online. We do not explicitly market to children below age 13.  
CAN-SPAM Act:  
We gather your email address from our site or where you have opted into a specific a relationship with us, our team and our customer support desk:

  * Respond to questions, Send information, and or other inquiries or questions.
  * Method orders and to send information and updates concerning to orders.
  * Market to our mailing list or proceed to send emails to our customers after the first transaction has happened.
  * Emails enable users to unsubscribe by applying the link at the end of every email.

**Contact Us**  
If you have any doubt in relation to this privacy policy you can you contact us using the information below. We in real apply all the mentioned policy. Use of the products and services of this site provides rise to no rights of activity for the different party against us, directly or indirectly, for faithfulness or otherwise. Our main contact is  
**support@socinator.com**
